nutritional-supplements-health-guide.com 2017-11-29

# Privacy Policy | Nutritional-Supplements-Health-Guide.com

Last Updated: July, 22, 2011

Nutritional-Supplements-Health-Guide.com strives to offer its visitors the many advantages of 

Internet technology and to provide an interactive and personalized experience. 

We may use Personally Identifiable Information (your name, e-mail address, 

street address, telephone number) subject to the terms of this privacy policy. 

We will never sell, barter, or rent your email address to any unauthorized third 

party. Period."

 **How we gather information from users**

How we collect and store information depends on the page you are visiting, 

the activities in which you elect to participate and the services provided. For 

example, you may be asked to provide information when you register for access to 

certain portions of our site or request certain features, such as newsletters or 

when you make a purchase. You may provide information when you participate in 

sweepstakes and contests, message boards and chat rooms, and other interactive 

areas of our site. Like most Web sites, Nutritional-Supplements-Health-Guide.com also collects 

information automatically and through the use of electronic tools that may be 

transparent to our visitors. For example, we may log the name of your Internet 

Service Provider or use cookie technology to recognize you and hold information 

from your visit. Among other things, the cookie may store your user name and 

password, sparing you from having to re-enter that information each time you 

visit, or may control the number of times you encounter a particular 

advertisement while visiting our site. As we adopt additional technology, we may 

also gather information through other means. In certain cases, you can choose 

not to provide us with information, for example by setting your browser to 

refuse to accept cookies, but if you do you may be unable to access certain 

portions of the site or may be asked to re-enter your user name and password, 

and we may not be able to customize the site’s features according to your 

preferences.

 **What we do with the information we collect**

Like other Web publishers, we collect information to enhance your visit and 

deliver more individualized content and advertising. We respect your privacy and 

do not share your information with anyone.

Aggregated Information (information that does not personally identify you) 

may be used in many ways. For example, we may combine information about your 

usage patterns with similar information obtained from other users to help 

enhance our site and services (e.g., to learn which pages are visited most or 

what features are most attractive). Aggregated Information may occasionally be 

shared with our advertisers and business partners. Again, this information does 

not include any Personally Identifiable Information about you or allow anyone to 

identify you individually.

We may use Personally Identifiable Information collected on Nutritional-Supplements-Health-Guide.com to communicate with you about your registration and customization 

preferences; our Terms of Service and privacy policy; services and products 

offered by Nutritional-Supplements-Health-Guide.com and other topics we think you might find of 

interest. 

Personally Identifiable Information collected by Nutritional-Supplements-Health-Guide.com may 

also be used for other purposes, including but not limited to site 

administration, troubleshooting, processing of e-commerce transactions, 

administration of sweepstakes and contests, and other communications with you. 

Certain third parties who provide technical support for the operation of our 

site (our Web hosting service for example) may access such information. We will 

use your information only as permitted by law. In addition, from time to time as 

we continue to develop our business, we may sell, buy, merge or partner with 

other companies or businesses. In such transactions, user information may be 

among the transferred assets. We may also disclose your information in response 

to a court order, at other times when we believe we are reasonably required to 

do so by law, in connection with the collection of amounts you may owe to us, 

and/or to law enforcement authorities whenever we deem it appropriate or 

necessary. Please note we may not provide you with notice prior to disclosure in 

such cases.

 **Affiliated sites, linked sites and advertisements**

Nutritional-Supplements-Health-Guide.com expects its partners, advertisers and affiliates to 

respect the privacy of our users. Be aware, however, that third parties, 

including our partners, advertisers, affiliates and other content providers 

accessible through our site, may have their own privacy and data collection 

policies and practices. For example, during your visit to our site you may link 

to, or view as part of a frame on a Nutritional-Supplements-Health-Guide.com page, certain content 

that is actually created or hosted by a third party. Also, through 

Nutritional-Supplements-Health-Guide.com you may be introduced to, or be able to access, information, Web 

sites, features, contests or sweepstakes offered by other parties. 

Nutritional-Supplements-Health-Guide.com is not responsible for the actions or policies of such third 

parties. You should check the applicable privacy policies of those third parties 

when providing information on a feature or page operated by a third party.

While on our site, our advertisers, promotional partners or other third 

parties may use cookies or other technology to attempt to identify some of your 

preferences or retrieve information about you. For example, some of our 

advertising is served by third parties and may include cookies that enable the 

advertiser to determine whether you have seen a particular advertisement before. 

Other features available on our site may offer services operated by third 

parties and may use cookies or other technology to gather information. 

Nutritional-Supplements-Health-Guide.com does not control the use of this technology by third parties or the 

resulting information, and is not responsible for any actions or policies of 

such third parties.

You should also be aware that if you voluntarily disclose Personally 

Identifiable Information on message boards or in chat areas, that information 

can be viewed publicly and can be collected and used by third parties without 

our knowledge and may result in unsolicited messages from other individuals or 

third parties. Such activities are beyond the control of Nutritional-Supplements-Health-Guide.com 

and this policy.

 **Children**

Nutritional-Supplements-Health-Guide.com does not knowingly collect or solicit Personally 

Identifiable Information from or about children under 13 except as permitted by 

law. If we discover we have received any information from a child under 13 in 

violation of this policy, we will delete that information immediately. If you 

believe Nutritional-Supplements-Health-Guide.com has any information from or about anyone under 13, 

please contact us at the address listed below.

Contacting Us.

We can be reached by contacting:

Nutritional-Supplements-Health-Guide.com

Email: nshg(at)nutritional-supplements-health-guide.com

Changes to this Policy

Nutritional-Supplements-Health-Guide.com reserves the right to change this policy at any time. 

Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of our site 

following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those 

changes. Information collected prior to the time any change is posted will be 

used according to the rules and laws that applied at the time the information 

was collected.

 **Governing law**

This policy and the use of this Site are governed by Turkey 

law. If a dispute arises under this Policy we agree to first try to resolve it 

with the help of a mutually agreed-upon mediator in the following location: 

Istanbul. Any costs and fees other than attorney 

fees associated with the mediation will be shared equally by each of us.

If it proves impossible to arrive at a mutually satisfactory solution through 

mediation, we agree to submit the dispute to binding arbitration at the 

following location: Istanbul,TR, under the rules 

of the American Arbitration Association. Judgment upon the award rendered by the 

arbitration may be entered in any court with jurisdiction to do so.

Nutritional-Supplements-Health-Guide.com is controlled, operated and administered entirely 

within Turkey. This statement and the policies outlined herein 

are not intended to and do not create any contractual or other legal rights in 

or on behalf of any party.
